<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!--			-- Ecologist --				-->

	<string id="ecolog_outfit_orn_name">
		<text>Closed suit "Ecologist"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_outfit_orn_description">
		<text>It is used by expeditions of scientists and environmental stalkers cooperating with them. It is not designed for combat operations, therefore it does not provide reliable protection from bullets or shrapnel.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecolog_outfit_grn_name">
		<text>Closed suit 첖yclops</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_outfit_grn_description">
		<text>A modified version of the previous sample. Ceramic-organoplastic armor panels have been added to protect the torso from bullet and shrapnel damage. This sample is designed to equip the protection of scientific expeditions.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Duty --				-->

	<string id="dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첗efender</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>A standard jumpsuit, modified specifically for the "Debt" grouping. It differs not only in coloring, but also in high-quality armor plates and additionally compacted fabric to resist various creatures of the Zone.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>Special suit 첔rmor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>A modified version of an early army jumpsuit for special units. It is distinguished by excellent radiation protection and high-class titanium plates. Part of the abnormal protection was redesigned to the detriment of the wearer of the jumpsuit, however, this made it possible to increase the convenience of wearing it.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Freedom --				-->

	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첳ind</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_description">
		<text>Lightweight stalker jumpsuit produced by artisans of the Svoboda group. It is used mainly by scouts and snipers, allowing you to quickly and silently change position. The protective characteristics leave much to be desired.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첯wift</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>Modification of regular army overalls with the use of artisanal technologies. To the detriment of the protective characteristics, it was possible to significantly increase the wearing comfort and reduce the weight of the jumpsuit itself.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Closed suit 첯pace</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>The management's attempts to independently study the Zone resulted in a joint experiment by one of the private companies and local artisans to create this jumpsuit. It has outstanding protective characteristics, but is unreliable in extreme conditions.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Loner --				-->

	<string id="novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_description">
		<text>An ordinary thick leather jacket, of which there are many. The skin provides little protection from fire or claws, but is completely useless against anomalies and radiation.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첯unrise</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>Produced by "folk craftsmen", the Sunrise suit is an effective combination of a lightweight army bulletproof vest and a jumpsuit made of aramid fabric. Despite the fact that the suit barely protects against pistol bullets, it is popular because of the low price and high potential for modification.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Closed suit 첯EVA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>The original abbreviation of this sample of Ukrainian research institutes turned into his nickname. Although the jumpsuit is designed to work under the influence of abnormal fields, it has very ordinary characteristics. Inexpensive, for which it is appreciated by local stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Exoskeleton 첟mpulse</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An attempt by one of the private companies to create the most affordable and cheap exoskeleton for veterans of the Zone and at the same time earn good money on it.</text>
	</string>	
	

<!--			-- Mercenary --				-->

 	<string id="merc_outfit_name">
    	<text>Suit 첕ear</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="merc_outfit_description">
    	<text>The standard coverall of a mercenary stormtrooper. It has good protection from bullets and shrapnel, but it is not adapted for conducting combat clashes in an abnormal zone.</text>
  	</string>

	<string id="merc_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첯cout</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>Lightweight jumpsuit, with good abnormal protection, produced by one of the little-known private companies. In general, it is much better protected than its analogues.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Closed suit 첖ornflower</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A suit for mercenary units designed specifically for performing tasks in areas with strong abnormal activity. It is equipped with a closed air circulation system and a built-in function of suppressing the actions of abnormal fields. It provides protection from bullet and shrapnel wounds, but it is not suitable for assaults and direct collisions.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Exoskeleton 첮etribution</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A high-quality exoskeleton of foreign commercial production. It has average protection indicators, but it gives extreme convenience to its carrier.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Monolith--				-->

	<string id="monolith_outfit_name">
        <text>Suit 첝ranite</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_outfit_description">
        <text>The manufacturer is unknown, most likely artisanal production. The structure resembles the coveralls widely distributed among neutral stalkers, in which a bulletproof vest is connected to a radiation protection suit. It protects well from weak small arms and abnormal activity.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_name">
        <text>Closed suit 첧rophet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_description">
        <text>Suit designed to work in abnormal fields, chemical and radiation pollution. It has a shatterproof vest of unknown origin, as well as unique modifications that reduce the effects of radiation.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_radiation_outfit_name">
		<text>Armored suit 첖rystal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_radiation_outfit_description">
		<text>One of the best personal protective equipment "Monolith". It has titanium plates with impurities of unknown substances, the analysis and synthesis of which were unsuccessful. It perfectly shields from radiation, but otherwise has cheap and low-quality materials.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_name">
        <text>Exoskeleton 첤onolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_description">
        <text>A semi-mythical jumpsuit, indicating a high technological base of manufacturers. It is focused on active combat operations. Someone assumes that this is an old development from Soviet times, while someone considers it a product of one of the private corporations. Any attempts to take possession of this jumpsuit ended in failure.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Bandit --				-->

	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Bandit Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>The traditional clothing of the bandit is a leather jacket with sewn armor elements. Provides some protection of the owner from harmful influences - however, extremely insufficient in the harsh conditions of the Zone.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Leather Raincoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>An ordinary cloak made of black leather. It does not provide special protection to the carrier, except that it will not let you freeze at night and will soften the bite of a blind dog. It is quite inconvenient, but nevertheless it is often used by bandits - perhaps solely because of its appearance.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첔ssault</text>
	</string>
	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_description">
		<text>Rumor has it that sometimes bandits do the dirty work of the same customers that work with mercenaries. Indirect proof of this is this jumpsuit.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Military --				-->

	<string id="specops_outfit_name">
		<text>Armored suit 첕eryl</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_outfit_description">
		<text>An army jumpsuit with an old-style uniform. It is not bad for conducting combat operations, but it protects from abnormal effects only by the basic properties of the material.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_outfit_name">
		<text>Special suit 첕ulat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_outfit_description">
		<text>A modern army armored suit for conducting assault operations in areas of abnormal activity. It is equipped with durable heavy-duty titanium plates, although it is not very comfortable to wear.</text>
	</string>

<!--			-- Helmet --				-->

	<string id="st_helm_balaclava">
		<text>Balaclava</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_balaclava_descr">
		<text>An ordinary black balaclava helps to protect the face from radioactive dust or hide it from unwanted glances.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator">
		<text>Gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_descr">
		<text>A standard gas mask designed to remove radioactive dust and toxic substances from the air. It is widely used by both beginners and veterans of all groups due to its functional indispensability. It is not equipped with protection against bullets, shrapnel and mechanical influences.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5">
		<text>Gas mask GP-5</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5_descr">
		<text>The GP-5 gas mask was intended to protect the civilian population of the Soviet Union from radioactive fallout and was manufactured during the Cold War from 1962 to 1989. It is a helmet-mask made of white and black rubber, the lenses are held in place by crimping rims. The lower part of the mask is made of metal, there are valves and a filter mount in it. GP-5 is widely used by loners and bandits because of its accessibility and low price.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_m40">
		<text>Gas mask M40</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_m40_descr">
		<text>This gas mask is the result of a program to develop a successor to the protective masks of the M-17 series, returning to the standard design with an external side arrangement of filters. The main innovation is that the filter can be installed both on the left and on the right. Equipped with a drinking system. It is ineffective with a lack of oxygen and in the presence of ammonia. It does not protect against abnormal activity, but it has a good bullet resistance. Often comes complete with mercenary coveralls.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_hardhat">
		<text>Steel helmet "Falcon"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_hardhat_descr">
		<text>An element of combat equipment of special units of the Ministry of Internal Affairs. It does not provide protection against anomalies or radiation, but is able to deflect a bullet that has arrived tangentially. The helmet kit includes not only the helmet itself, but also anti-shatter glasses. He was in demand in the Zone only during the first clashes between the factions.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_tactic">
		<text>Kevlar helmet "Sphere"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_tactic_descr">
		<text>A modern, high-quality Western-style helmet with a built-in air filtration system. Designed to provide the unit commander with the maximum amount of tactical information when installing the appropriate electronic "stuffing". It is characterized by a reinforced construction, also equipped with a multi-layer Kevlar protection, an XM40 gas mask and a first-generation night vision device.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_battle">
		<text>Kevlar helmet "Sphere-M"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_descr">
		<text>The helmet is trimmed with titanium-aluminum fabric, which provides good protection from firearms, as well as minor protection from psi radiation. The kit includes an armored mask with a built-in respirator and a first-generation PNV. Supports the installation of one 40 mm filter from the PMK series gas masks. The M12 is one of the most reliable helmets available in the Zone. Its main task is to protect the owner's head, however, at the cost of considerable additional weight.</text>
	</string>

<!--			Backpacks				-->

	<string id="st_equ_backpack_name">
		<text>Backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_backpack_desc">
		<text>An ordinary waterproof backpack. It is popular among stalkers who make forays deep into the Zone.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_equ_duffel_bag_name">
		<text>Duffel bag</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_duffel_bag_desc">
		<text>An ordinary hiking duffel bag. It accommodates a lot, but it is very uncomfortable, which makes the body get tired quickly. It weighs almost nothing.</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_equ_small_pack_name">
		<text>Small pack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_small_pack_desc">
		<text>A frequent attribute of newcomers who drag them from outside the perimeter. There is practically no capacity, but you can comfortably place it on your back and not worry about the loss of swag.</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_equ_tourist_pack_name">
		<text>Tourist backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_tourist_pack_desc">
		<text>A good sample in terms of price / quality ratio. It fits like a duffel bag, while it is relatively comfortable to carry on your back, although it is still far from ideal.</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_equ_military_pack_name">
		<text>Army Backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_military_pack_desc">
		<text>You don't often meet such people in the military themselves, and they don't need them. Basically, it is an attribute of various mercenaries and special purpose groups. Very expensive, but accommodates a lot while distributing the weight evenly over the body, from which you practically do not get tired.</text>
	</string>	

<!--			Special				-->

	<string id="csky_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Suit 첖S-2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_outfit_description">
		<text>This body armor was developed for conducting search operations in areas with low abnormal activity. The use of fairly high-quality materials has increased the resistance to wear. Equipped with two containers for artifacts.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_name">
		<text>Camouflage suit "Owl"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_description">
		<text>A camouflage jumpsuit that is designed for special army sniper units. It is distinguished by the presence of protection from abnormal effects and dense high-quality fabric.</text>
	</string>		
	
</string_table>
